import 'package:quiz_practice/models/question.dart';

final level1QuestionList = [
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 1',
    options: [
      'Question 1 Option 1',
      'Question 1 Option 2',
      'Question 1 Option 3',
      'Question 1 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 1 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 2',
    options: [
      'Question 2 Option 1',
      'Question 2 Option 2',
      'Question 2 Option 3',
      'Question 2 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 2 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 3',
    options: [
      'Question 3 Option 1',
      'Question 3 Option 2',
      'Question 3 Option 3',
      'Question 3 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 3 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 4',
    options: [
      'Question 4 Option 1',
      'Question 4 Option 2',
      'Question 4 Option 3',
      'Question 4 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 4 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 5',
    options: [
      'Question 5 Option 1',
      'Question 5 Option 2',
      'Question 5 Option 3',
      'Question 5 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 5 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 6',
    options: [
      'Question 6 Option 1',
      'Question 6 Option 2',
      'Question 6 Option 3',
      'Question 6 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 6 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 7',
    options: [
      'Question 7 Option 1',
      'Question 7 Option 2',
      'Question 7 Option 3',
      'Question 7 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 7 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 8',
    options: [
      'Question 8 Option 1',
      'Question 8 Option 2',
      'Question 8 Option 3',
      'Question 8 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 8 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 9',
    options: [
      'Question 9 Option 1',
      'Question 9 Option 2',
      'Question 9 Option 3',
      'Question 9 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 9 Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 1 Question 10',
    options: [
      'Question 10 Option 1',
      'Question 10 Option 2',
      'Question 10 Option 3',
      'Question 10 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 10 Option 1',
  ),
];

final level2QuestionList = [
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 1',
    options: [
      'Question 1 Option 1',
      'Question 1 Option 2',
      'Question 1 Option 3',
      'Question 1 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 1 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 2',
    options: [
      'Question 2 Option 1',
      'Question 2 Option 2',
      'Question 2 Option 3',
      'Question 2 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 2 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 3',
    options: [
      'Question 3 Option 1',
      'Question 3 Option 2',
      'Question 3 Option 3',
      'Question 3 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 3 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 4',
    options: [
      'Question 4 Option 1',
      'Question 4 Option 2',
      'Question 4 Option 3',
      'Question 4 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 4 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 5',
    options: [
      'Question 5 Option 1',
      'Question 5 Option 2',
      'Question 5 Option 3',
      'Question 5 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 5 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 6',
    options: [
      'Question 6 Option 1',
      'Question 6 Option 2',
      'Question 6 Option 3',
      'Question 6 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 6 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 7',
    options: [
      'Question 7 Option 1',
      'Question 7 Option 2',
      'Question 7 Option 3',
      'Question 7 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 7 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 8',
    options: [
      'Question 8 Option 1',
      'Question 8 Option 2',
      'Question 8 Option 3',
      'Question 8 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 8 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 9',
    options: [
      'Question 9 Option 1',
      'Question 9 Option 2',
      'Question 9 Option 3',
      'Question 9 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 9 Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 2 Question 10',
    options: [
      'Question 10 Option 1',
      'Question 10 Option 2',
      'Question 10 Option 3',
      'Question 10 Option 4',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Question 10 Option 2',
  ),
];

final level3QuestionList = [
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 1',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 2',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 3',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 4',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 4',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 1',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 5',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 6',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 4',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 7',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 2',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 8',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 3',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 9',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 3',
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Level 3 Question 10',
    options: ['Option 1', 'Option 2', 'Option 3', 'Option 4'],
    correctAnswer: 'Option 2',
  ),
];
